Kyouma,
I want...
...you to be...
（岡部倫太郎(おかべりんたろう)）ハッ
...the messiah.
ハアッ　フッ
フハハハ フハハハハ…
この俺が救世主だと？
You want me to be the messiah?
Ridiculous.
くだらん　俺は狂気の
マッドサイエンティスト
I'm a mad scientist...
望みは破壊と混沌(こんとん)だ
I desire chaos and destruction!
ハハッ　ハハハハハ…
（橋田 至(はしだいたる)）
どうしちゃったんだぜ？
What's up with him?
フッ
We'll now resume Operation Urd.
これより
オペレーションウルドを再開する
え？ 下にまだブラウン氏いるけど
Mr. Braun's still downstairs, man.
（岡部）かまわん
I don't care!
（牧瀬紅莉栖(まきせくりす)）
待って　言ったはずよ
Wait!
I told you.
私は反対
I'm against this.
Against what?
（岡部）何を…
昼間は協力的だったではないか
Just this morning, you were helping me.
（橋田）昼間って？
（岡部）うっ…
This morning?
Then... I knew it.
それじゃ やっぱり…
Yes.
ああ　実験は行われた
The experiment already happened.
Ｄメールにより
すでに過去は変わっているのだ
The D-mail changed the past.
（橋田）マジっすか？
Seriously?
世界線が変わったっていうこと？
The world line changed?
I think so.
（岡部）
おそらくな　そのためにお前たちは
改変前の記憶を一部 失ったのだ
Thus, you've lost some of your memories from before the change.
（橋田）それって
例のロト６(シックス)がどうとかってやつ？
Is this about that Lotto 6 thing?
That's right.
そうだ
So why are you the only one who remembers?
…で どうしてあんただけが
記憶を保っているのよ
（岡部）タイターは言っていた
俺には力があると
Titor told me that I have the power.
それを確かめるためにも もう一度
世界線を移動させねばならないのだ
To prove it, we'll need to move world lines again.
The power?
力？
The power to retain memories, even across world lines...
世界線を越えてなお
記憶を持ち続ける力
The magic eye: Reading Steiner.
魔眼(まがん)　リーディング･シュタイナー
～
Chaos Theory
Homeostasis
（漆原(うるしばら)るか）ハア…
フウ…
（電話レンジのベル）
（岡部）ダル
Daru?
There's no record in the outbox...
（橋田）送信履歴なし　着信は…
But as for the inbox, the D-mail arrived five days ago.
おお　Ｄメールは５日前に届いてる
It succeeded.
成功ね
Did the past change?
過去 変わった？
フッ　なぜ そのことを覚えている
Why do you remember that?
（橋田･紅莉栖）あ…
We sent a D-mail to Daru five days in the past
（岡部）５日前のダルに
Ｄメールを送り
telling him the position of the cards, so he could win the Feyris Cup.
フェイリス杯での
カードの配置を知らせ―
ダルが優勝するはずが…
（橋田）ああ まゆ氏？
Mayushii?
Quick question: in the Feyris Cup last week...
ちょっと聞きたいんだけど
この前のフェイリス杯で僕って…
What? I lost? Immediately?
え？ 負けた？ 瞬殺？
I see... Thanks. Bye.
あ… そう
サンキュー　じゃあ
はあ…
Daru's message didn't alter the past.
（岡部）ダルのメールでは
過去は変わらなかった
With the way the game went, it should've changed.
ゲームの流れは変わったはずよ
It wasn't enough to change world lines.
それくらいでは
世界線は変動しないということだ
Then we need an easier way to tell if the past has changed.
もっと分かりやすく
過去が変わったと―
確認できるものでないとダメか…
ほう？
I-It's not like I suddenly agree with these experiments, okay?
べ… 別に実験に賛成とか
そういうことじゃなくて
…で どう思ってるの　あんただけ
記憶が継続してることについて
So what do you think?
About you being the only one to remember?
I told you.
言ったはずだ
It's the power of the magic eye, Reading Steiner!
魔眼 リーディング･シュタイナーの
力だと
あ？
In order to see if that's true,
それを確かめるためにも次は
お前にＤメールを送ってもらうぞ
I'll have you send the next D-mail.
I'd rather not.
私はイヤ
Worried about a time paradox?
（岡部）タイムパラドックスが
気になるのか？
It feels unfair to change the past.
過去を変えるなんて
なんか ひきょうな感じがするから
I've only lived 18 years, but I wouldn't change any of it.
私の人生は たかだか18年だけど
改変なんかしたくない
They're all part of my life, even the failures.
失敗したことも含めて
自分の人生なんだから
（岡部）だが 実験は大好き
そうだな？
But you love experiments, right?
す… 好きで悪いか？
I-Is that so wrong?
In other words, you'll just sit back and watch as others sacrifice themselves.
すなわち自分は高みの見物を決め
他人を犠牲にして ほくそ笑む
A true mad scientist.
うむ　実に
マッドサイエンティストだ
Enough!
もういい
But seriously...
しかしだ 真面目な話…
（岡部）ん？
Please
I want to send a D-mail too !
Moeka
But seriously, if we're going to perfect the D-mail...
真面目な話 Ｄメールを
より完璧にするため…
Please ?
It's okay, right ?
Please !
Moeka
くっ やはり実験を続けるしか…
...we'll have to continue our experiments...
I'm...
A lab member too, right ?
Moeka
Kiryuu?
（紅莉栖）桐生(きりゅう)さん？
ええい　くどい
Enough!
I can't?
（桐生萌郁(もえか)）ダメ？
（岡部･紅莉栖）わあっ
（岡部）あーあ…
She overwhelmed us...
結局 押し切られてしまった
Okay, we're here!
（天王寺裕吾(てんのうじゆうご)）
はーい　おうちに着きました　ハハ
Those crêpes were good...
（天王寺）クレープおいしかったな
（天王寺 綯(なえ)）うん
Yeah!
Hey! You look bored.
（天王寺）何だ 暇そうじゃねえか
I'm waiting for someone.
（岡部）人を待ってるんですよ
（綯）うっ…
Hey, don't scare Nae!
（天王寺）オラッ
綯を怖がらせるんじゃねえって
I didn't do anything!
何もしてないでしょう
Come on, Nae.
さあ 綯　こんな野郎
相手にしないで さっさと行こうな
Let's leave this loser alone and go inside.
Hi!
（椎名(しいな)まゆり）おはよう
わあっ
Big sis Mayuri!
（綯）まゆりお姉ちゃん
（２人）トゥットゥルー
フフッ
This is for you.
これ あげる
Thanks!
わあ　ありがとう
（岡部）フッ
Here's one for Okarin too!
（まゆり）はい　オカリンにも
フフッ
フッ
ん？
Yo!
（阿万音鈴羽(あまねすずは)）ちーっす
Good morning, Suzu.
鈴(すず)さん　おはよう
It's the part-timer girl!
バイトのお姉ちゃん
Hey... What happened after that?
ねえねえ　あれからどうしたの？
何がだ
With what?
The time machine!
タイムマシンだよ
ジョン･タイターに聞いたの？
Did you ask John Titor?
Yeah, but I don't know if what he says is accurate...
ああ　だが やつの言うことが
正しいのかどうか―
分からなくなってきた
えー！ どの辺が？
Which part?
あ？ なぜ そんなにムキになる
Why are you so interested?
あ…
You're a Titor fanatic, aren't you?
お前 さてはタイターオタだな
違うって
That's not it.
（まゆり）ああ 紅莉栖ちゃん
トゥットゥルー
Kurisu!
Good morning.
グッドモーニング
（鈴羽）あっ
（岡部･まゆり）あ？ ん？
（紅莉栖）あ…
（橋田）ほおー
また火花を散らせていたわけですか
More sparks between you two?
What's her problem, anyway?
（紅莉栖）何なのよ　まったく
Fighting makes me sad.
ケンカは悲しいです
あ… 心配しないで 大丈夫だから
Don't worry! It's okay.
Thank you.
（萌郁）ありがとう
私的なメールは禁止だ
No private messages.
We want something simple that'll make it clear
過去が変わったかどうか
確認しやすい―
whether the past has changed.
シンプルな内容が望ましい
"I changed my cell phone four days ago,
（岡部）“４日前に
携帯の機種変更したけど―”
and I want to tell myself not to do it."
“変えないほうがよかったって
自分に伝えたい”
I see.
なるほど　過去が変われば
桐生さんの携帯が変わる
So if the past changes, you'll have a different cell phone.
It'd be obvious.
一目瞭然ね
Then let's begin the experiment!
では 実験を開始する
（まゆり）えいっ
All right! Activate the Phone Microwave (name subject to change)!
（岡部）よし！
「電話レンジ（仮）(かっこかり)」起動
（一同）ん？
It's so round...
（まゆり）まん丸だー
（岡部）これは？
What's this?
岡… 凶真(きょうま)さんに頼まれたロト６
間違えてしまったので
I used the wrong number for the Lotto 6 you asked me about.
This is my apology.
その おわびです
I... I see.
お？ おお
そ… そうか　それは…
（紅莉栖）ん？
（岡部）うむ　よい心がけだ
Good... Good to hear!
The day nears when your heart's eye will open.
お前の心眼が開く日も
遠くはないだろう
Yes!
はいっ　じゃあ 僕はこれで…
Well, if you'll excuse me...
You're leaving?
もう行っちゃうの？
なんだか
お取り込み中みたいですし
You seem busy.
（岡部･紅莉栖）あっ
Goodbye.
失礼します
Wear Mayushii's cosplay sometime soon, okay?
（まゆり）
今度は まゆしぃのコス
着に来てよね
I-I'm sorry.
ご… こめんなさい
僕 そういうのはちょっと…
I'm not really into that...
So you won't?
（まゆり）やっぱりダメ？
似合うと思うんだけどな
I think you'd look great...
Goodbye.
じゃ また
うん　バイバイ
Bye-bye!
フッ
Good kid, huh?
いい子ね
Yeah.
うん
（萌郁）ああっ
（岡部）うわっ　うぐっ
ううっ　うっ
This feeling again.
（岡部）また この感覚？
ということは…
Which means...
the past has changed?
過去が変わった？
（まゆりの鼻歌）
あ…
シャ… シャイニング･フィンガーは
どこへ行った？
Wh-Where's Shining Finger?
Shi...
シャイ… はあ？
Japanese, do you speak it?
日本語でオケ
ハッ　ハアッ
（まゆりの鼻歌）
（岡部）ハッ
Rukako didn't stop by?
るか子は来なかったのか？
Rukako? Nope.
（まゆり）
るか君？ うん　来てないけど
Then Moeka... Where's Moeka?
（岡部）
では萌郁は？ 萌郁はどうした
Moeka? Who's that?
（まゆり）萌郁さん？ 誰？
（岡部）ハッ
桐生萌郁だ
今日は来ていないのか？
Kiryuu Moeka!
She wasn't here today?
Well?
（岡部）どうなんだ？
（まゆり）ええっ？
Who's that?
それ 誰？
（岡部）ハッ
Kiryuu Moeka... I've never heard that name before.
桐生萌郁？
私も聞いたことがない
What?
何だと？
ハッ　まさか またＤメールを？
Another D-mail?
えっ ちょっ…
それ どういうこと？
Wh-What do you mean?
The past changed, and Moeka's very existence was erased?
（岡部）過去が変わり―
萌郁という人間の存在
そのものが消えた
まさか…
Impossible!
Up to July 31st, my inbox still has messages from her.
（岡部）着信履歴には７月31日まで
萌郁のメールが残っている
（震える息）
（岡部）ハッ
（岡部）“どうかした？ ゴメン
今 ちょっと忙しくて―”
"Something wrong?"
"Sorry, I'm kind of busy."
"I'll message you later."
“後でメールするね”
ハアッ
In other words, four days ago,
（紅莉栖）つまり４日前
メールを受け取ってからの―
this Kiryuu Moeka who sent that message changed her actions,
桐生… 萌郁さん？
彼女の行動が変わり―
and never came to the lab.
ラボには来なかったというふうに
過去が改変された
The past has changed.
I suppose so.
そういうことだな
And this time, only you remember it.
それに 今回も
あんただけが覚えている その…
The Reading Steiner, was it?
リーディング･
シュタイナーだっけ？
By the way, just saying that is embarrassing.
ちなみに この造語 恥ずかしい
やめたほうがいいと思う
I don't think you should call it that.
I'm not interested in your personal opinion.
お前の個人的な見解は必要ない
（紅莉栖）ハア…
The power to retain memories across world lines.
世界線を越えて記憶を継続する力…
Is it for real?
ホントに本物なの？
Here I am!
（まゆり）お待たせ
We'll talk tomorrow.
話は またあした
See you tomorrow, Okarin!
オカリン　またあした
I really do have that ability.
（岡部）この力は本物だ
I want you to be the messiah.
That means...
では… 俺は？
I...
I'm amazed they can sleep at the lab.
（紅莉栖）まったく あいつら
よくラボで寝泊まりできるわよね
He said it's because he's a mad scientist.
（まゆり）それが
マッドサイエンティストなんだって
I know! Let's all sleep over at the lab next time!
そうだ　今度 みんなで
お泊まり会しようよ
Only if the guys aren't there.
男ども抜きならね
そうだ　私のホテルに来ない？
I know. Why not come to my hotel?
Can I really?
いいの？
Of course.
もちろん
Sure!
（まゆり）
うん　じゃあ今度 お邪魔するね
Okay, I'll come over soon!
ん？
Ruka?
るか君　トゥットゥルー
Yeah...
うん　うん　ええっ？
Yeah... What?!
Really?
本当？
What?!
（岡部）なにっ？
You didn't bring the Magical Blade Samidare?
妖刀五月雨(さみだれ)を
持ってこなかっただと？
Um...
（るか）あの…
（まゆり）ダメだよ　オカリン
Don't say that, Okarin!
Today, Ruka is my guest.
（まゆり）るか君は今日は
まゆしぃのお客さんなんだよ
He's going to wear my cosplay!
まゆしぃのコスを
着てくれるんだね？
Um... I...
（るか）ぼっ 僕…
Come on. Let's transform, Ruka. Transform!
（まゆり）
さあさあ　るか君 変身しよう
変身 変身
Um, I mean, I...
（るか）あっ だ… だから僕…
Let's take off your clothes...
（まゆり）ほら 服を脱ぎ脱ぎして
（るか）
ああっ そんな所 触らないで
No, don't touch me there!
Okay!
分かった　僕一人で着るから
だから あっちに…
I'll put it on myself,
so allow me!
You have to know the trick to putting this on.
（まゆり）
これ 着るのにコツがいるからね
P-Please... don't take off my clothes!
（るか）お願いだから脱がさないで
This is quite lesbian.
（橋田）すごく 百合(ゆり)です
Except Rukako's a guy.
（岡部）違うな　るか子は男だ
Which makes it...
（橋田）ということは…
even better!
さらに けしからん
エヘッ
（るか）ああ…
（２人）うっ…
It's Kirari from Rai-Net.
（まゆり）
雷(らい)ネットのキラリちゃんだよ
あっ　ハア…
You're as cute as I imagined, Ruka!
思ったとおり
カワイイよ るか君
This is really embarrassing.
こんな格好 恥ずかしい
It's okay!
大丈夫
“カワイイは正義”だから
Cuteness is justice!
I want to get a low-angle shot of this.
（橋田）これは
ローアングラー化したくなる
What do you think, Okarin?
（まゆり）オカリンは どう思う？
（２人）うーん
That's right...
（岡部）そうだな…
おおっ ううっ
俺だ　今 強烈な精神攻撃を受けた
It's me!
I've just been victimized by a fierce psychological attack!
くっ　マズい
心が 心が侵食されて…
This is bad!
My soul... My soul is being devoured!
Wh-What's wrong, Kyouma?
（るか）
ど… どうしたんですか？ 凶真さん
What's with him?
また何を騒いでるんだか
Kurisu!
紅莉栖ちゃん　トゥットゥルー
（紅莉栖）ん？
Stop staring, my perverted assistant.
（岡部）変態助手よ　全身を
ねめ回すように見つめるのはよせ
I'm not staring!
してないわよ
Even more win!
（橋田）またも けしからん展開
What do you think of this cosplay?
どう このコス
るか君に似合ってる？
Does it look good?
え？ ええ…
とってもキュートね
Yes, it's very cute.
C-Cute... Well, I...
キュ… キュートだなんて
そんな…
Let's try on the others!
ほかの衣装も着てみよう
ああ　待って
Wait!
I came here because I had a request for you.
今日 ここに来たのは―
凶真さんたちに
お願いがあったからなんです
You didn't come here to wear my cosplay?
（まゆり）コスを着に
来てくれたんじゃなかったの？
I-I said, "No," but you wouldn't listen to me...
ち… 違うって言ってるのに
話を聞いてくれないんだもん
I'm sorry. I was just really happy.
（まゆり）あ… ごめんね
うれしくって つい
So what did you want to ask?
で 頼みというのは？
あの 実は…
Actually...
（岡部）うん
I want you to let me send a message to the past!
僕も過去にメールを
送らせてほしいんです
（３人）えっ？
Yesterday...
（るか）昨日…
I came by to apologize for messing up the Lotto 6, but before I could...
ロト６を外してしまったおわびを
しようと思って そしたら…
Another D-mail?
（紅莉栖）
まさか またＤメールを？
（橋田）えっ ちょっ…
それ どういうこと？
Wh-What do you mean?
The past changed, and Moeka's very existence was erased?
（岡部）過去が変わり―
萌郁という人間の存在
そのものが消えた
まさか…
Impossible!
I'm sorry for eavesdropping when I shouldn't have!
（るか）すみませんでした
盗み聞きするつもりなんて
なかったんですけど
I didn't mean to!
Ruka, what kind of message do you want to send to the past?
るか君　過去に
どんなメールを送りたいの？
Actually, I...
実は 僕…
I want to be a girl!
女の子になりたいんです
（紅莉栖）は？
（岡部･橋田）え…
I don't like the way I look.
僕 自分の容姿が
あんまり好きじゃなくて
I think I'd feel better about myself if I was a girl...
女の子になれれば
少しは自信が出るかなって―
I've always felt that way.
昔から そう思ってたんです
W-Wait a second...
ちょ ちょ… ちょっと待って
What is she saying?
いったい 彼女は何を言っているの
フフン　助手よ　どうやらお前は
決定的な間違いを犯しているようだ
Assistant, you appear to have made a fatal mistake.
間違い？
Mistake?
Rukako is no girl.
るか子は女ではない　男だ
He's a guy.
What kind of joke is that?
何の冗談だ それは？
You don't believe me...
浅はかだな　お前も科学者なら
自分の目でしっかり確かめてみろ
If you call yourself a scientist, then see for yourself.
ん…
Such a cute girl couldn't be a guy.
こんなカワイイ子が男の子のはず…
Excuse me for a second.
ごめん　ちょっと…
ハッ
（まゆり）大丈夫？
Are you okay?
I'm serious!
（るか）僕 本気なんです
本気で女の子になりたいんです
I really want to be a girl!
Please!
お願いします
But I don't know if sending a D-mail
（岡部）しかし
Ｄメールを送ったところで―
would be enough to change your gender.
性別を変えることなど
できるかどうか…
I heard about this thing...
聞いたことがあるんです
If you eat lots of meat when a baby is in your tummy,
赤ちゃんが
おなかにいるあいだに―
お肉をいっぱい食べると
男の子が―
you'll have a boy.
With a lot of vegetables, you'll have a girl.
野菜をいっぱい食べると
女の子が生まれるって
You want us to send a D-mail telling your mom to eat lots of vegetables?
（紅莉栖）お母さんに“野菜を
いっぱい食べてね”って―
Ｄメールを送るってこと？
Would that be possible?
はい　ダメでしょうか？
Very well.
よかろう
お前の望みをかなえてやろう
I shall grant your wish.
ハッ　ありがとうございます
Thank you!
Good for you, Ruka!
（まゆり）よかったね　るか君
（るか）はい
Yes!
Isn't changing someone's gender a bad idea?
性別を変えるなんて
さすがに マズいんじゃね？
Do you think it's possible to affect it
野菜を食ったぐらいで
そんなことがありえると思うか？
just by eating vegetables?
True enough.
（紅莉栖）
そうね　科学的な根拠が
ある話でもないし…
There's no scientific evidence for it.
He must've really been worried about it
悩んだうえでのことだろう
それで気が済むのなら…
if that made him feel better.
Rukako, from now on, you're Lab Member 006!
るか子
今日からお前は わがラボの一員
ラボメンナンバー００６だ
Y-Yes.
は… はい
Let's begin the experiment...
さて 早速 実験を… おっ
Wait. You're 17 this year, right?
お前 今年17だったな
Huh? Yes.
えっ？ はい
In other words, you were born in 1993.
つまり1993年生まれ…
So what?
それが どうかしたの？
When did cell phones become popular in Japan?
携帯電話が日本に
普及し始めたのは いつごろだ？
（紅莉栖･橋田）あ…
It looks like it was around 1996,
（橋田）1996年ごろっぽい
and only later did they get messaging capabilities.
メールの機能がつくのは
さらに遅いかも
In other words, when he was born,
つまり
漆原さんが生まれた時点では―
there's a good chance his mom didn't own a cell phone.
お母さんが携帯電話を
持っていない可能性がある
Then we can't send the D-mail?
じゃあ Ｄメール送れないの？
Oh, no...
そんな…
We could change it, so it sends sinister microwaves.
（橋田）
毒電波を飛ばせるように
改造するとか？
You have enough sinister microwaves for everyone.
毒電波は あんたたちだけで十分
Good... Insult me more.
ああ いいよ
もっと ののしってくれて
オーケーだよ
That's the stuff...
I see.
そうか　フフフフフ…
アーハッ　自分の才能が恐ろしい
I'm terrified by my own talent!
Not this again...
また何を言いだすんだか
If she doesn't have a cell phone, send it to her pager!
携帯がないのなら
ポケベルに送ればいいじゃない
Pagers...
（紅莉栖）
“ポケベル　電波によって”
A system using EM waves to transmit messages to small receivers.
“小型受信機に
合図を送るシステム”
During the 1990s, they enjoyed enormous popularity.
“1990年代に爆発的に普及”
The emergence of cellular phones rendered them obsolete.
“携帯電話の普及により
下火となる”
Pagers?
（まゆり）ポケベル？
I've never seen one!
（るか）これが… 初めて見ました
You're very knowledgeable.
詳しいな
セレセブならぬ セレサーか？
I guess you're a Cell-Pager, not Cel 7?
It's written right there.
そこに書いてある　自分で読め
Why not read it yourself?
あ… ん？
Lab Member 006, Urushibara Ruka!
ラボメンナンバー００６ 漆原るか
ファーストミッションだ
It's time for your first mission.
Find out if your mother had a pager
母親がポケベルを持っていたか調べ
その番号を入手せよ
and acquire that number!
Y-Yes, sir!
は… はいっ
My mom had a pager!
（るか）
お母さん ポケベル持ってました
Here's the number.
これが番号です
You did it!
（岡部）でかしたぞ
You've thought about what to write, right?
メールの文面は
考えてきたのだろうな
はい
Yes!
"Consume vegetables for a healthy child."
（岡部）
〝やさい たべると
げんきなこをうめる〞
I heard you can only send 18 hiragana...
ひらがなで18文字しか
送れないと聞いたので
You can only send numbers to a pager.
（紅莉栖）
ポケベルは数字しか送れないのよね
To transform these to numbers...
これを数字に変換して…
One sec.
（橋田）ちょい待ち　濁点は
数字２個で表現しないとダメっぽい
You need two digits for voiced consonants.
（るか）え？
What?
You can send a total of 36 English letters.
送れるのは半角で36文字まで
その文章だと４文字オーバー
That message puts you four characters over.
I see... Then...
ふむ　では…
Consume veggies for a healthy child.
Consu veggies for a healthy child.
Con veggies for a healthy child.
veggies for a healthy child.
E veggies for a healthy child.
Ea veggies for a healthy child.
How about we turn this into numbers?
（岡部）これを数字に変換すると…
Eat veggies for a healthy child.
Okay, starting it up.
いいか　起動するぞ
はい
All right.
Is this really okay?
本当に大丈夫かな
心配するな
Don't worry about it.
（岡部）うっ…
（るか）ハッ　うっ
うあっ うっ…
ハッ
My Reading Steiner activated!
（岡部）
リーディング･シュタイナーが
発動した
That means...
ということは…
ハッ
I see... Some people are like that, huh?
（紅莉栖）なるほど
こういう人もいるのね
Yes, it's cute!
（まゆり）
うん　これはカワイイです
Ruka, I think you'd look great in something like this.
るかちゃんには
こういうの絶対 似合うと思うな
（るか）そ… そうかな
Y-You think?
（岡部）ん？
This is...
（岡部）これは…
You pervert!
（紅莉栖）コラ 変態
どこを見つめている
Where are you staring?
（まゆり･るか）はっ？
No, I mean...
いや そうではなく うっ…
Wait.
（岡部）待てよ　るか子は
女になれたかとは聞きづらい
It's difficult to ask if Rukako became a girl.
However...
しかし…
This failed.
これは失敗だな　ハア…
Just what kind of perverted things are you imagining?
だから ニヤニヤと いったい
どんな変態的行為を想像している
Geez, Okarin!
もう オカリン
I can't take my eyes off you two perverts for a minute.
まったく あんたたち変態コンビは
油断も隙もないんだから
I'm not a pervert! I'm a perverted gentlemen!
（橋田）変態じゃないよ
変態紳士だよ
It doesn't matter! It honestly doesn't matter!
（紅莉栖）どうでもいい
ホント どうでもいい
But...
（岡部）だが…
the world line changed.
確かに世界線は移動した
何かが変わったのだ
Something happened...
but what?
いったい 何が？
～